[Music]
Allah
[Applause] Good
evening everyone.
Thank you for inviting me to this ICI Lambard free helmet distribution. So we interacted with the school children here. We
came and made them aware of the importance of helmets. So we have
given them free of cost and saved a
life. So
ICI Insurance Company has given 3
lakhs of helmets all over India.
In 15 cities, they have saved 3 lakhs of lives.
If you look at the traffic aspect, they have saved 15
lakhs. So
in Chennai, they
have given 9000 helmets. So why are we
starting this from our school zone? There are
many rules and terms and
conditions.  We are following
this school and
we
are giving this to the next generation, keeping in mind that there will be a clear generation. So,
parents who attended this event and those who are
watching this, if you are a road user, please be aware of
the terms and
conditions and
drive on the road accordingly. Thank you, Chennai Police.
[Music]